My Resume



Georgios Papadopoulos

Aspiring Web Designer / Geek

- geopap910@gmail.com
 - Greek
 - https://geoter711.github.io/online-cv/
- Geoter711
- Resume PDF

Languages

- Greek (Native)
- English (Professional)

Interests

- Gaming (Video and Tabletop)
- Informatics
- Data Analysis
- Human Behavior and Psychology

Career Profile

My first experience of working an IT job was with a private IT company which I still work to this very day as a part-timer. Currently as a web designer, the frontend end has definitely interested me more than the backend. Down the line I would like to further expand upon that, and perhaps find more interests. As a

youth I also used to work a summer job in a restaurant located in Paleokastritsa, Corfu, Greece.

Education

Undergraduate Student

2019 - Present

Ionian University, Department of Informatics

Even though many other options presented themselves, I opted to study in Ionian University due to both its location (since I'm a local) and because of its great curriculum and possibilities it provides. So far I've gravitated towards bringing humanistic studies in my studies, introducing elements of computer design and the interaction between human and computer, as well as how humans act and interact with both themselves and computers. Main interests include:

- Web and Computere design
- Graphical Interfaces
- Human Computer Interaction
- Networking

Experiences

Intern

2021 - Present

Webits, Corfu

I work as an intern, often undertaking many projects geared around web designing, mostly via the use of CSS, HTML and PHP. I'm still learning many things on the specifics!

Waitor

2019 - 2020

Nereids Restaurant, Corfu

Worked during the summer months of 2019 and 2020, giving me more insight about how a workplace environment operates. Got to meet many people, polish my social skills and acquired many interesting experiences. Learned a couple of bar tricks too.

Projects

I don't particularly have any projects, considering that what I've done for the most part is through the company, but I have worked on a university project with a fellow student. Technically still in progress, it is a visual novel game using

Ren'Py, where I undertook some roles including character design, management of said project, and fleshing out parts of the dialogue and code.

Proficiency in Programming Languages

HTML5 & CSS
PHP

Javascript & jQuery
C++
SQL
Java
C
Python

Designed with by Xiaoying Riley